Break the jar, Tim." I looked at my other hand. With the setting sun and the rainy sky,
I swear the jar glowed brighter than any street light near me. I didn't break it because I was
following her instruction. I broke it because I was angry. I broke it because I was upset.
I needed a release. I raised my arm above my head and brought it down with one swift motion,
shattering the jar on the concrete beneath my feet. That dark, chilly air accompanying the
rain spread away like it was the shockwave of a bomb going off, and I was at the epicenter.
I saw the warm, yellow light from inside the jar spread rapidly across the ground and ascend into
the sky. It was as if I was watching the beginnings of the universe being created,
like God had just snapped his fingers and said, let there be light. I was engulfed in it. I could
no longer see street, or rain, or anything dark. I felt like I was plummeting into a star going
faster than the speed of light. It felt like sitting in front of a fire on a cold winter's
night, but that warmth was covering every inch my body. And then I blinked. Immediately I could feel
the sheets beneath me, and my back barely touching my wife's. I was staring out the window. The
morning light drenched through the glass and gleamed on my face. I stood from bed and grabbed
my phone. It was Friday morning. I had one text, let me know if you ever need another jar. I called
in sick to work. I snuck into my daughter's room and greeted her with a kiss and told her she
didn't have to go to preschool today. We were going to have a family day. She smiled and stretched
out her arms with a yawn before curling up and falling back asleep. I got back in bed and
squeezed my wife tightly. I didn't let go for hours. Our daughter came into our room and woke
us up eventually, she was jumping on the bed and shouting for us to wake up. Yesterday I may have
found that annoying. Yesterday I may have found a lot of things annoying, or monotonous, or dull.
But not today. Today, I pulled her under the covers in between me and Kelsey.
Today was going to be a good day. Today, I was happy.